Guide to the William Saroyan Papers, 1926-1981
Department of Special Collections
- Manuscripts, 1928-1981., Series 5
  - Short Stories, Subseries 5.03
    - Palo: TS, corrected; TS carbon; tearsheet,1950 (Carton 65, Folder 1)
    - The Parachute Jump: TS, corrected,1940 (Carton 65, Folder 2)
    - Paramount, Please Let Me Act: Tearsheet, corrected,1934 (Carton 65, Folder 3)
    - Paris and Philadelphia: Tearsheet,1950 (Carton 65, Folder 4)
    - Paris is the Place for You: TS carbon, corrected; tearsheet; galley,1961 (Carton 65, Folder 5)
    - The Parsley Garden: TS, corrected,1949 (Carton 65, Folder 6)
    - The Parsley Garden: Titled "A California Story," TS carbon, 2 copies,1950 (Carton 65, Folder 7)
    - The Parsley Garden: Educational materials (Carton 65, Folder 8)
    - The Peaceful and Poetic Year: Tearsheet,1940 (Carton 65, Folder 9)
    - The Pebble Cove: TS, corrected,1962 (Carton 65, Folder 10)
    - The Personal Secretary: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1960 (Carton 65, Folder 11)
    - Pete: TS, corrected,1935 (Carton 65, Folder 12)
    - The Pheasant Hunter: TS, corrected; tearsheets,1949 (Carton 65, Folder 13)
    - Piano: TS, corrected,1937 (Carton 65, Folder 14)
    - Picnic Time: Tearsheets,1973 (Carton 65, Folder 15)
    - Picnic Time: Titled "The Private Fight," TS, corrected; TS carbon,1964 (Carton 65, Folder 16)
    - The Pinochle Player: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 17)
    - The Poet Ashamed: TS, corrected; TS carbon; tearsheet,1949 (Carton 65, Folder 18)
    - The Poet At Home: TS, corrected; galleys,1949 (Carton 65, Folder 19)
    - The Pomegranate Trees: TS, corrected; tearsheet,1937 (Carton 65, Folder 20)
    - The Poor and Burning: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 65, Folder 21)
    - Pop: Titled "Two Cups of Coffee at the Automat," TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies,1964 (Carton 65, Folder 22)
    - The Pop-Corn Man: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1940 (Carton 65, Folder 23)
    - The Presbyterian Choir Singers: TS, corrected,1939 (Carton 65, Folder 24)
    - The Protectors of Culture: Tearsheet,1940 (Carton 65, Folder 25)
    - Radical Meeting: Tearsheet,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 26)
    - Raisins: TS,1934 (Carton 65, Folder 27)
    - The Reader of the World Almanac for 1944: Titled "The New Coat," TS carbon, 2 copies,1950 (Carton 65, Folder 28)
    - The Reader of the World Almanac for 1944: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 29)
    - The Rearward Dog: TS, corrected; galleys,1950 (Carton 65, Folder 30)
    - The Red Roses: Titled "The Full House," TS, 2 copies,1961 (Carton 65, Folder 31)
    - The Red Roses: TS carbon, corrected, 2 copies; TS titled "The Farmer's Story" ,1962 (Carton 65, Folder 32)
    - The Rescue of the Perishing: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1950 (Carton 65, Folder 33)
    - The Rich and the Poor: TSS, corrected, 2 copies; carbon TS, corrected,1973 (Carton 65, Folder 34)
    - Sailing Down the Chesapeake: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies,1938 (Carton 65, Folder 35)
    - Sailing Down the Chesapeake: Published in The Coast,1938 (Carton 65, Folder 36)
    - Sailing Down the Chesapeake: Misc. notes,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 37)
    - Salute the Man, Joe, He's From San Francisco: TS carbon, 3 copies,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 38)
    - The Same as Twenty Years Ago: Tearsheet,1938 (Carton 65, Folder 39)
    - Science Fiction You Are So Clever: TS carbon, corrected,1974 (Carton 65, Folder 40)
    - The Sea and the Small Boy: Titled "A Whole Day of Gladness," TS, corrected; TS carbon,1952 (Carton 65, Folder 41)
    - The Sea and the Small Boy: Tearsheet,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 42)
    - Seven Fragments: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 65, Folder 43)
    - Seventy Thousand Assyrians: Galley photocopy; misc. notes,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 44)
    - Shag Mugger's Drive: TS carbon, 2 copies; proof sheet; clipping,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 45)
    - A Short History of Wild Life and Lunatic Letters in America: Titled "Tatiana and Rudolfo, Lovers Forever," TS; TS carbon,1974 (Carton 65, Folder 46)
    - A Short History of Wild Life and Lunatic Letters in America: Mimeo, corrected,1975 (Carton 65, Folder 47)
    - Short Story to Order: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 48)
    - Short Visit Home and Travel: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 65, Folder 49)
    - Shout Armenia Wherever You Go: Galleys; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 65, Folder 50)
    - Shower Down and Sleep in the Streets: TS, 1938 (Carton 65, Folder 51)
    - Small Accidents: TS, 1949 (Carton 65, Folder 52)
    - A Small Boy with a Large Curiosity: Titled "All I Ever Wanted Was My Share," and "My Fair Share," TS; mimeo; corrected, 1975 (Carton 65, Folder 53)
    - A Small Boy's Adventures: A Memoir: TS, revised; tearsheet, 1950 (Carton 65, Folder 54)
    - A Small Boy's Adventures: A Memoir: TS carbon, 1950 (Carton 65, Folder 55)
    - The Small Rain: Titled "A Lot of Rain," TS corrected; TS carbon, 1956 (Carton 65, Folder 56)
    - The Small Trouble That Starts at Home: TS, corrected, 1937 (Carton 65, Folder 57)
    - Snakepeace and Cricketeater: TS; TS carbon, corrected, 1974 (Carton 65, Folder 58)
    - Something Unimportant - If Not Apocryphal: Tearsheet,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 59)
    - The Song: TS, corrected, 1937 (Carton 65, Folder 60)
    - The Spaniard: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1961 (Carton 65, Folder 61)
    - The Spaniard: TS carbon, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 62)
    - Speck, the Special Sardine: TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected, 1952 (Carton 65, Folder 63)
    - Speck, the Special Sardine: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 64)
    - Speck, the Special Sardine: Titled "The Lonesome Sardine," TS carbon, 1954 (Carton 65, Folder 65)
    - Speck, the Special Sardine: Galley proofs; tearsheet, 1956 (Carton 65, Folder 66)
    - Stanley Rose and the Unknown Writer: Titled "Charley Chaplin Did a Dance," TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies, 1964 (Carton 65, Folder 67)
    - Stanley Rose and the Unknown Writer: Titled "A Little of the World Around Stanley Rose's Book Store...," TS photocopy, 1970 (Carton 65, Folder 68)
    - Stanley Rose and the Unknown Writer: Tearsheet, 1975 (Carton 65, Folder 69)
    - Stanley Rose and the Unknown Writer: Misc. title pages, 1970 (Carton 65, Folder 70)
    - Still Life with Fish: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies, 1952 (Carton 65, Folder 71)
    - The Stolen Bicycle: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1939 (Carton 65, Folder 72)
    - The Stork Club Blues: TS, corrected; tearsheet, 1940 (Carton 65, Folder 73)
    - The Story of the Man Who Fell Out of a Tree: Tearsheet, 1972 (Carton 65, Folder 74)
    - Strangers and Enemies: TS, corrected, 1948 (Carton 65, Folder 75)
    - The Stumblebums: TS,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 76)
    - The Suez Canal Affair: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies, 1956 (Carton 65, Folder 77)
    - A Summer Day: Tearsheet, 1936 (Carton 65, Folder 78)
    - The Summer of the Beautiful White Horse: TS, corrected; notes, 1937 (Carton 65, Folder 79)
    - The Summer of the Beautiful White Horse: TS carbon; tearsheets, 1956 (Carton 65, Folder 80)
    - The Sunday Zeppelin: Titled "Sunday," TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 65, Folder 81)
    - The Survivor of the Influenza Epidemic of 1918: TS, corrected, 2 copies; TS carbon, 1939 (Carton 65, Folder 82)
    - The Sweepstakes Winner and Grapes in the Winter: TS,n.d.: (Carton 65, Folder 83)
    - The Swimmers: TS, corrected; TS carbon; tearsheet, 1964 (Carton 65, Folder 84)
    - Take Her to Vegas: Titled "The Mayan or the May Marriage of a Mayan," TS, TS carbon, galley; Tearsheet, 1961 (Carton 66, Folder 1)
    - A Talk with Father: TS photocopy,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 2)
    - The Talking Man: TS, corrected, 1947 (Carton 66, Folder 3)
    - Thank You Very Much For Everything and Don't Worry: Tearsheet, 1961 (Carton 66, Folder 4)
    - The Theological Student: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies, 1947 (Carton 66, Folder 5)
    - There Was A Young Lady of Perth: TS; TS carbon; tearsheet, 1961 (Carton 66, Folder 6)
    - There's One in Every School: Tearsheet; photocopy, 1972 (Carton 66, Folder 7)
    - There's One in Every School: Titled "A School for Pitchers," TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected, 1950 (Carton 66, Folder 8)
    - There's One in Every School: Titled "The Good Boy and the Bad Boy," TS carbon, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 9)
    - There's One in Every School: Titled "The Celebration at Trancas," TS, corrected; TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 10)
    - There's One in Every School: Titled "Celebration at Tagus," TS, corrected, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 11)
    - There's One in Every School: Titled "Getting Along at School," TS carbon, corrected; galleys, 1971 (Carton 66, Folder 12)
    - They are Talking About Me: TS, 1973 (Carton 66, Folder 13)
    - This is Not a Story: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1964 (Carton 66, Folder 14)
    - The Three Instructions, and the Evil Step-Mother and the Beautiful Step-Daughter: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 15)
    - The Three Swimmers and the Grocer from Yale: TS, corrected; TS carbon; tearsheet, 1939 (Carton 66, Folder 16)
    - Three Wagons: TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected, 2 copies, 1953 (Carton 66, Folder 17)
    - The Time Before: TS; tearsheet, 1938 (Carton 66, Folder 18)
    - Time Together: TS carbon, corrected, 3 copies, 1963 (Carton 66, Folder 19)
    - To Be Courteous to Women: TS carbon; proof sheets; galleys, 1962 (Carton 66, Folder 20)
    - The Tooth and My Father: TS, corrected; TS photocopy, 1968 (Carton 66, Folder 21)
    - The Tooth and My Father: Setting copy, 1973 (Carton 66, Folder 22)
    - The Tooth and My Father: Galleys, 2 sets, 1974 (Carton 66, Folder 23)
    - The Trains: Tearsheet,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 24)
    - Trig Tratatat: TS carbon, 3 copies, 1965 (Carton 66, Folder 25)
    - Trig Tratatat: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1964 (Carton 66, Folder 26)
    - Trig Tratatat: Mimeo TS, corrected, 2 copies, 1974 (Carton 66, Folder 27)
    - The Turk Street Gamblers: Titled "The Gambling Writers of San Francisco," TS, corrected, 1955 (Carton 66, Folder 28)
    - Twenty is the Greatest Time In Any Man's Life: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies, 1964 (Carton 66, Folder 29)
    - Twenty is the Greatest Time In Any Man's Life: Galley; tearsheet, 1977 (Carton 66, Folder 30)
    - 26 Ways to Write a Story: Tearsheet, 1971 (Carton 66, Folder 31)
    - Two Old Armenian Stories and One New One: TS, corrected, 1939 (Carton 66, Folder 32)
    - Two Pies for a Quarter: TS, corrected; tearsheet, 1937 (Carton 66, Folder 33)
    - The Two Thieves: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 34)
    - Uncle Silly and the Problem of the Writer: TS carbon, 2 copies, 1962 (Carton 66, Folder 35)
    - Unfortunate Accident at the Fox Theater: TS, revised, 1929 (Carton 66, Folder 36)
    - The Unpublished Writer, Rain, and His Daughter: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 37)
    - Up Mike's: TS, corrected, 1947 (Carton 66, Folder 38)
    - The Veteran of Foreign Wars: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1947 (Carton 66, Folder 39)
    - A Visitor in the Piano Warehouse: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1954 (Carton 66, Folder 40)
    - Vorotan's Madness: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1966 (Carton 66, Folder 41)
    - The War: Tearsheet, 1972 (Carton 66, Folder 42)
    - The War Against the Microbes: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1939 (Carton 66, Folder 43)
    - The War in Europe: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 44)
    - A Warning to Boys: TS carbon, corrected, 1949 (Carton 66, Folder 45)
    - A Wedding Photograph: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 3 copies, 1964 (Carton 66, Folder 46)
    - A Wedding Photograph: Galleys; tearsheet, 1976 (Carton 66, Folder 47)
    - We're Armenians, the Little Boy Said: Titled "The Loser," TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies, 1966 (Carton 66, Folder 48)
    - We're Armenians, the Little Boy Said: Titled "We're Armenians, Ash Said," TS carbon, corrected; photocopies, 1972 (Carton 66, Folder 49)
    - We're Armenians, the Little Boy Said: Mimeo; TS photocopy, corrected, 1972 (Carton 66, Folder 50)
    - A Western Killing of Forty Years Ago: TS, corrected; tearsheet, 1937 (Carton 66, Folder 51)
    - What a World, Said the Bicycle Rider: TS, corrected, 1962 (Carton 66, Folder 52)
    - What a World, Said the Bicycle Rider: TS carbon, corrected; tearsheet, 1962 (Carton 66, Folder 53)
    - What to Do: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 1949 (Carton 66, Folder 54)
    - What's the Matter with the Human Face?: TS, corrected, 2 copies, 1949 (Carton 66, Folder 55)
    - A Whole Stupid Rigmarole: TS carbon, 2 copies (Carton 66, Folder 56)
    - The Whole Voyald and Heaven Itself: TS, corrected, 1953 (Carton 66, Folder 57)
    - The Whole Voyald and Heaven Itself: Titled "Father & Son," TS carbon; tearsheets, 1955 (Carton 66, Folder 58)
    - The Whole Voyald and Heaven Itself: Galleys,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 59)
    - Wolfgang, a Story: TS; photocopy, 1974 (Carton 66, Folder 60)
    - Wonderful America: TS, corrected, 1940 (Carton 66, Folder 61)
    - A Word to Scoffers: TS; TS carbon; tearsheet, 1935 (Carton 66, Folder 62)
    - Write Jokes, ... Tell Jokes... Make Everybody Laugh: Titled "Dinner with Mark Twain," TS carbon, 2 copies; tearsheet, 1969 (Carton 66, Folder 63)
    - Yea and Amen: TS, edited,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 64)
    - Yes, Johnny, There Will be Baseball in Heaven: TS, corrected, 2 copies; TS carbon, 1963 (Carton 66, Folder 65)
    - The Young and Loving: TS, revised, 1938 (Carton 66, Folder 66)
    - The Young and Loving: The Young Husband and Father: TS, corrected, 1938 (Carton 66, Folder 67)
    - The Young and Loving: A Young Man Walking: TS, 1935 (Carton 66, Folder 68)
    - The Young and Loving: The Young Man Who Signed the Coupon: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 69)
    - The Young and Loving: The Young Organizer Who Finds Meaning in Life by Fighting for His Beliefs: TS, corrected, 1937 (Carton 66, Folder 70)
    - The Young and Loving: You're Breaking My Heart: Titled "You're Driving Me Crazy," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 66, Folder 71)
  - Essays, Subseries 5.04
    - The Cult of Cuteness
    - A Friendship (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Haphazard Questions (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - How About the Awards for Barbers and Bootblacks (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - How Many Sides to the Human Question (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Intellectuals Gain Recognition (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Is This the Cagey Age?(see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - It's Human to be Stupid Sometimes (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - On Getting Things in Order (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Prestige or Pay (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Saroyan Predicts Nixon as Next President (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Saroyan Puts U.N. to Work!(see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Scalawag's Heaven (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - The Small Business (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - Truth, Nothing but the Truth (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - The TV Poll Hysteria (see: For the Record, miscellaneous) (see: For the Record, miscellaneous)
    - About Teeth and Dentists: TS, edited; galley; tearsheet,1976 (Carton 67, Folder 1)
    - The Adventure: TS, corrected,1948 (Carton 67, Folder 2)
    - Ah Life, Ah Death, Ah Music, Ah France, Ah Everything: TS,1936 (Carton 67, Folder 3)
    - Almost Last Words: TS, corrected,1977 (Carton 67, Folder 4)
    - The Alphabet Book: TS,1979 (Carton 67, Folder 5)
    - The Alphabet Book: TS photocopy,1979 (Carton 67, Folder 6)
    - Alphonse: TS, corrected, 2 copies; TS carbon,1964 (Carton 67, Folder 7)
    - Alphonse: Titled "Alphonse, or the Death of a Small Boy," TS carbon, 2 copies,1965 (Carton 67, Folder 8)
    - Alphonse: Misc.,1965 (Carton 67, Folder 9)
    - Alphonse: Galleys; tearsheets,1972 (Carton 67, Folder 10)
    - Alphonse: Galleys,1972 (Carton 67, Folder 11)
    - The American Dream: TS; tearsheet,1976 (Carton 67, Folder 12)
    - Americans: Tearsheet,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 13)
    - Another Cold Day: TS,1955 (Carton 67, Folder 14)
    - Another Day, Another Dream: TS, corrected,1937 (Carton 67, Folder 15)
    - Applause: Tearsheet,1955 (Carton 67, Folder 16)
    - Apple Pie & Crazy People: TS, corrected; tearsheet; galleys,1969 (Carton 67, Folder 17)
    - An Appropriate Chore for Inauguration Day: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies,1957 (Carton 67, Folder 18)
    - An Appropriate Chore for Inauguration Day: TS carbon, corrected,1957 (Carton 67, Folder 19)
    - April 27 in Paris: TS, corrected,1949 (Carton 67, Folder 20)
    - Are Writers Worth Listening To?: TS carbon; galley; tearsheet,1955 (Carton 67, Folder 21)
    - Around the World, and Death, and Back Again: TS carbon, corrected; tearsheets; galley,1964 (Carton 67, Folder 22)
    - Around the World with General Grant: TS,1936 (Carton 67, Folder 23)
    - The Arrogant London Fly of 1944: TS, corrected,1956 (Carton 67, Folder 24)
    - Art for Man's Sake: TS, corrected; tearsheet; galley,1955 (Carton 67, Folder 25)
    - The Art of Being a Man: A Primer of Life: TS,1931 (Carton 67, Folder 26)
    - Art, or on Account of Orozco: TS, corrected; tearsheets; galleys,1954 (Carton 67, Folder 27)
    - The Arts (and Upstarts) in America: TS, corrected; TS carbon, edited,1961 (Carton 67, Folder 28)
    - The August Hobo Silently Down the Street: TS carbon, corrected,1962 (Carton 67, Folder 29)
    - The Bell by Guy de Maupassant: TS, corrected, 2 copies; TS carbon, in French; galleys; tearsheet, French,1959 (Carton 67, Folder 30)
    - The Big Bores: TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected,1954 (Carton 67, Folder 31)
    - The Big Change, or Consider the Hippopotamus, Thou Mouse: TS, corrected; setting copy; galley; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 67, Folder 32)
    - The Big Fight: Titled "About the Fight," TS, corrected; TS carbon; galleys; tearsheets,1971 (Carton 67, Folder 33)
    - A Big Plate of Rice and Meat is Not Too Much for Me At All: TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected; mimeo, corrected; photocopy,1971 (Carton 67, Folder 34)
    - A Big Plate of Rice and Meat is Not Too Much for Me At All: TS, 3 copies; tearsheet; galley,1971 (Carton 67, Folder 35)
    - A Big Plate of Rice and Meat is Not Too Much for Me At All: Titled "What's So Funny?," TS, corrected; mimeo,1972 (Carton 67, Folder 36)
    - Births: TS, corrected; notes,1979 (Carton 67, Folder 37)
    - Births: TS photocopy, corrected,1979 (Carton 67, Folder 38)
    - Births: TS photocopy,1979 (Carton 67, Folder 39)
    - Bitlis: TS, corrected; photocopy,1967 (Carton 67, Folder 40)
    - Bitlis: TS carbon,1967 (Carton 67, Folder 41)
    - Bitlis: TS carbon, corrected,1967 (Carton 67, Folder 42)
    - Bitlis: Misc. notes,1967 (Carton 67, Folder 43)
    - The Body: TS carbon, corrected,1936 (Carton 67, Folder 44)
    - Boredom in the Army: TS, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 45)
    - Bores of 1962: TS, corrected; tearsheet,1962 (Carton 67, Folder 46)
    - A Boy Sets a Stage: TS,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 47)
    - Bread, Water, Salt and Soul: Titled "About Eating," TS, corrected; TS carbon; TS, corrected, titled "Eating and Eaters,"1963 (Carton 67, Folder 48)
    - Bread, Water, Salt and Soul: TS carbon, 3 copies,1965 (Carton 67, Folder 49)
    - Broadway Squawk: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies,1961 (Carton 67, Folder 50)
    - But Ronald Reagan Can't Act: TS; TS photocopy, corrected,1980 (Carton 67, Folder 51)
    - C.A.T. Cat Spells Everything: Titled "The Word and My Life," and "The Word and the Writer," TS, corrected; TS carbon,1957 (Carton 67, Folder 52)
    - The Cabbages Flung at the Door: TS, corrected,1949 (Carton 67, Folder 53)
    - California: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1958 (Carton 67, Folder 54)
    - The Celebrated Jumping State of California: TS, corrected,1964 (Carton 67, Folder 55)
    - The Celebrated Jumping State of California: TS carbon, 2 copies,1948 (Carton 67, Folder 56)
    - The Celebrated Jumping State of California: Mimeo TS, corrected, 2 copies,1973 (Carton 67, Folder 57)
    - The Celebrated Jumping State of California: Tearsheet,1974 (Carton 67, Folder 58)
    - Celebrities Don't Die, They Drop Out of the Celebrity Register: TS, corrected,1974 (Carton 67, Folder 59)
    - Chorus: TS, corrected,1949 (Carton 67, Folder 60)
    - Christmas: TS,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 61)
    - The Comedian: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 67, Folder 62)
    - The Comedian at Omar Khayyam's: TS, corrected,1939 (Carton 67, Folder 63)
    - The Comic Page and Vital Statistics: TS, corrected,1935 (Carton 67, Folder 64)
    - The Comic Page and Vital Statistics: TS carbon, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 65)
    - Composition for Mr. Pound: TS photocopy,1933 (Carton 67, Folder 66)
    - Confessions of a Playwright: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1948 (Carton 67, Folder 67)
    - Confessions of a Playwright: Published in World Review,1949 (Carton 67, Folder 68)
    - Confessions of a USO Sneakthief: TS, 2 copies,1980 (Carton 67, Folder 69)
    - A Couple of Miscellaneous Prophecies, More or Less Guaranteed to Come True: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 67, Folder 70)
    - Creativity in the Theater: TS,1965 (Carton 67, Folder 71)
    - Credo: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 72)
    - The Crookedest Man I Ever Met: TS carbon; tearsheet,1955 (Carton 67, Folder 73)
    - The Crying Man of Paris: TS, corrected; TS carbon, 2 copies; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 67, Folder 74)
    - Death and Music: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 67, Folder 75)
    - Death and Syncopation: Tearsheet,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 76)
    - Decision on the 19, 131st Day: TS carbon, corrected; galleys; tearsheet,1963 (Carton 67, Folder 77)
    - Destroying the Individual: Tearsheet; galley,1973 (Carton 67, Folder 78)
    - Don't Forget to Write: Tearsheet; TSS (2) (Carton 67, Folder 79)
    - A Drive With the Kids: TS, corrected; galleys,1954 (Carton 67, Folder 80)
    - Easter Laughter: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 81)
    - The End of the War and Robert Burns: A Shorty Story: TS carbon, corrected, 5 copies; galleys,1959 (Carton 67, Folder 82)
    - The End of the World: Tearsheet,1936 (Carton 67, Folder 83)
    - Epistle to the Armenians: TS, corrected; photocopy,1977 (Carton 67, Folder 84)
    - Event of Enormous Beauty: Titled "GOP Convention," galleys,1964 (Carton 67, Folder 85)
    - The Fable of the War Between the Old Complex and the New Culture: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 67, Folder 86)
    - The Failure: TS, corrected,1948 (Carton 67, Folder 87)
    - The Fair Out West: TS,1939 (Carton 67, Folder 88)
    - Fame, Fortune, Fat and Fate: TS, corrected; tearsheet,1966 (Carton 67, Folder 89)
    - Famous Americans and Their Homes: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 67, Folder 90)
    - A Few Answers About Television: Titled "Television Art," TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected; TS carbon titled "Movies vs. Television,"1953 (Carton 67, Folder 91)
    - A Few Remembered Armenians: TS,1967 (Carton 67, Folder 92)
    - Fight for Life: TS,1935 (Carton 67, Folder 93)
    - The 500 Year Plan: TS,1954 (Carton 67, Folder 94)
    - "For the Love of God, Boys, Girls, Lay Off These Christmas Stories About Supersensitive Kids, Won't You?: Titled "The Dostoyevsky Story," TS, corrected; TS carbon,1964 (Carton 67, Folder 95)
    - "For the Love of God, Boys, Girls, Lay Off These Christmas Stories About Supersensitive Kids, Won't You?: Tearsheet; galleys,1976 (Carton 67, Folder 96)
    - Four Hours for Irish Writing: TS carbon, corrected; galleys,1952 (Carton 67, Folder 97)